Good morning, dear.
I'm going now.
Right. Have a safe walk.
Hey, how's it going, Tani?
Yamada.
As in, word to Yamada.
You're Suzuki's friend. Did she tell you?
Whoa, sharp instincts.
It's the only thing that could explain your energy.
Well, my theory is that if you like Suzuki, then you'll like me, too.
Hmm. I had planned to keep this quiet. So much for that.
Huh? Why's that?
If the wrong people at school find out, it wouldn't be good for her image.
Bruh.
What?
We're talking about Suzuki?
You put her on a high pedestal.
Damn, dude.
Ah, of course you do.
What am I saying? You're a man in love.
But if she's kissing and telling you, you can too, pal.
Plus, it's no secret. Everybody saw her blurt out that she loved you, then zoomed right out of the classroom.
What?
Yeah. That stunt got all of us rooting for you guys.
Sato, Watanabe, Capacho.
Who's that last one?
Oh, and while Suzuki's image isn't going to decline or whatever, your entertainment value just gained some serious points.
Entertainment value?
This has been nice. You're easy to talk to.
Hey, man. Compliments won't get you squat.
Except for Pucket Kitty.
That's not squat.
And then, Suzuki can slip the heroin into his arms and whisper, baby, you rock my world.
Isn't that so romantical?
Oh, I thought that would kill.
Fictional couples are like the farthest thing from my mind right now.
Come on, girl. You owe us a big update.
I am a victim of shoujo manga turned live action drama mania.
Yeah, I hear it's a real epidemic.
You always talk about how sexy, sexy, hot, hot Sudaken is. Such a bad boy. Blah, blah, blah.
Well, let's be honest.
She's right.
You talk a bit game.
But you're totally coolest when it comes to interacting with guys.
I am painfully aware.
You want to line him up for the home runs, but you only pick strikeouts.
Hey, here's an article. Looks promising.
Be a good listener. Talking nonstop can make your siggo feel unheard.
Ask good questions about the things you know he's into.
Great couples pay attention.
Leaving your boyfriend hanging might make him insecure.
Sure. As his girlfriend show interest in what he has to say.
Oh boy, I've got hardcore work to do.
Girlfriend.
Boyfriend.
Couple.
Everybody back up.
She's off the rails again.
I'm so happy.
Weird. I'm so annoyed.
I do.
We literally just got together and the ship's already sinking.
Holy mood swings.
It's settled.
My new mission is to become king of the girlfriends.
And now she's a shonen protag.
So, what's your move, king of the GFs?
Today, I'll have to walk home together.
Oh my god, cute.
Sine, cosine, tangent.
心の角度が広がって
電流が走る一目惚れ
覚えていてフレーニング
純度100%の想いも
一心伝心させたいな
君とあたしは正反対
恋はいつも想定外
ねえねえ聞いて
言葉を尽くして君に伝えたいの
心が体に追いついて
気付けば目で追ってる
眼鏡を外してさ
ちゃんと目を合わせてよ
恋は走り出しても
放課後まで待ってない
大しな言葉ほど
酸素を嫌うみたい
辞書にないあたしなりの言葉で
早く
君に伝えたいの
今ねえ
ご視聴ありがとうございました
今の場合は
え?
ご視聴ありがとうございました
Uh, hi, so do you want to walk home with me?
Oh my god, we're walking home alone together!
We're a new couple!
We're walking this way too, you weirdo.
Have a good night, Suzuki.
You too!
Later!
Bye!
Happy other productive practice right now!
Hell of a jazz square you've got going on there, Suzuki.
Did anybody see Tai?
Jesus, like he wasn't even there.
I'm playing back all of our interactions in my head.
And I've totally been talking at him instead of to him.
I haven't asked Tani anything about his hobbies or interests.
I'm a monster.
Hang on.
It looked like you wanted to say something just now.
A GOLDEN OPPORTUNITY!
WATCH UP! SMOOL IT!
SMOOL IT!
Oh, um, it's nothing.
Forget it.
What?
Zero last question.
Why, boy, no answer.
The more I think about it, the less I know how to act like a normal person.
Is being with me right now even remotely fun for him?!
Hearting is such sweet sorrow.
I wasted major potential.
Bye.
Suzuki, I need to talk to you.
Got a sec?
Yamada came to talk to me this morning.
Huh?
For why?
Did he say something stupid?
No.
He was actually really friendly.
It was nice.
Good, cause the man's a yapper.
Before, I figured we would keep our relationship quiet.
It just surprised me is all.
I'm sorry!
Was I supposed to keep it a secret?!
Crap!
My emotions were so big I had no choice but to vomit them all up!
Vomit them up?
Sounds painful.
Wait, he's laughing?!
I don't mind if it's a secret or not.
It doesn't change anything to me.
But earlier, you said you were afraid of what others would think,
so I just assumed.
Of course you'd say that.
Tani, you're just so...
I am such an idiot.
So hung up on stupid rules and social norms that I can't even hold a conversation.
I've been so lost in my thoughts, I haven't even looked at him!
I don't care what they think!
I mean, last week I would've been a little bit freaked out,
but I'm not now!
I've only got one life,
so I want to like the stuff I like and love the person that I love!
That's you!
I'm sorry.
I was trying to be comforting.
Did I just come off super scary?
Uh, no.
Hey, so were you free this weekend?
Hello?
If you'd like, maybe we could go to that place you mentioned.
The hamburger!
Holy crap, we harmonized!
We have the same brain!
I thought it'd be nice to try it.
That would be awesome!
And afterwards we should go somewhere we can hang out and talk!
Right.
Let's see our options.
Oh, you're freaking horses, cowboy!
Tawny, explain.
I can't.
Was that an illusion?
I wish it was, but I'm just pathetic.
Dude!
You just keep getting cuter!
Please just leave me.
No way, man!
I'll never forget what I just saw!
Those searches mean you're thinking about me!
Even when I'm not around it, that makes me so happy I could just die!
I thought I was the only one flipping out about this, so I'm glad you're excited too!
Hey, Suzuki.
I love you too.
There...
I wanted to tell you before.
I felt it, but I couldn't say it.
Huh?
For real?
The thing he was trying to tell me earlier...
Was that he loves me?
Vapor?
Well, it's common scientific knowledge that 60% of Suzuki is made up of water!
That goes for everyone.
Hey, let's add a movie to our date!
I noticed you looked up the times!
Kill me.
Rather not!
I screamed so much my throat got all scratched up!
It was very intense.
I bet if I sing right now I'll sound so sick!
Maybe some candy would help?
Oh, yeah!
Give me that!
We're so sweet, it makes sense!
Your pockets are full of sugar!
Thanks a ton.
They aren't really wise.
I feel like someone's talking about me.
Who'd do that?
I'm happy for you.
Our very first date pinched me now!
No offense, but I can't imagine you and Tawny walking around in the wild.
Me neither.
Take some pics for us!
What?
Stalker shots of Tawny?
Shots of you together!
No!
I would be way too embarrassed to ask him now!
Your bar for embarrassment is truly a mystery.
Now that you got a BF, you gotta learn how to smile for pictures!
But that one's a total thirst trap.
You could drink soup out of those dimples.
Is that what you think a thirst trap is?
I see.
Stop forcing dimples.
It makes your face look weird.
This is a huge photo op.
You gotta get it just right.
I'll try.
Freaky face aside.
What the heck do you wear to a burger slash movie date?
I don't know what kind of clothes Tawny likes on me.
I gotta find something in here that's undeniably cute!
Something anybody would like!
I was so anxious I got here half an hour early!
My nerves are at an all-time high!
I'm gonna be a sweaty mess before he gets here!
Maybe I duck into a shop?
No, I can't do that.
What if I zone out and wind up being late?
Ooh, I wonder what else that Tawny picked out.
Suzuki.
Oh, hey Tawny!
You beat me. Sorry.
Just as stupidly handsome as always!
I would've hurried if you had called me.
No, I didn't want to make you rush.
Besides, you're still early.
My goal was to arrive exactly ten minutes before you.
But we're twenty minutes early.
Hmm.
Yay! It's finally here!
Holy God, that is massive.
A behemoth.
Thank you for the meal!
Wait!
The last time I was here, look at you getting down and dirty!
Drum!
What is it?
Well, you're a very tidy and polite eater. It's high-key impressive.
Well, I'm not a little kid. You haven't tried it yet.
Well, are you the burger police?
Well, you dissected it.
Yeah, I don't want you to see me shove the whole thing in my face. I'm still trying to up my charm factor with you.
I understand, but... won't that mess with the flavor?
You've got a good point.
Flavor over flirting!
We've got time to kill before the movie, so let's wander.
Is there anything you've had your eye on or any shops you want to sneak a peek in?
No.
Bouncing between random places it is, then.
Mm-hmm.
I'm still trying to up my charm factor with you.
I understand, but... won't that mess with the flavor?
You've got a good point.
Flavor over flirting!
Ah!
We've got time to kill before the movie, so let's wander.
Is there anything you've had your eye on or any shops you want to sneak a peek in?
No.
Bouncing between random places it is, then.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, hey! It's already time!
The unauthorized recording and distribution of this copyrighted work is illegal.
Criminal copyright infringement is punishable by up to ten years in prison.
Sorry. What was that?
That didn't say anything.
I didn't say anything.
Oh, hey!
Sorry. What was that?
You didn't say anything.
The
Dieting!
You and your friends!
Stay cool!
That was adorable!
I live for a post-credits scene!
I even cried a little!
Hang on! One sec!
Just girl stuff!
Yikes! Full raccoon!
Gotta get quick! Much longer and he'll think
I'm dropping off the kids at the pool!
Thanks for waiting on me, Tani!
Take some pics for us!
Sorry to bother you, but could you take our picture?
Cute!
Say cheese!
As if!
The time between me asking and them taking the picture is lethally awkward!
Suzuki.
Do you wanna shop?
For sure!
Aw, it's the fluffball from the movie!
Oh yeah, the Yeti.
They even have the witch and the little bears!
How cute!
These things...
People buy them as mementos, right?
Souvenirs?
Would they up my charm factor...
With... you?
My 700 mil!
Interesting metric.
Who says you need a photo to record a happy memory?
Remember where the protag lived?
Would you call it a village or a town or...
Who cares? It was so cute!
Halcyon Town?
Yeah! Love that place!
I was geeking out over the pretty illustrations of that spot up north!
North Island.
My favorite character was the babiest fluffball.
Yeti?
The scene where the whole fam gathered together was so cutesy!
I wish I could remember their names!
Gotek, Nit, Boa, Godin, Heatek.
What?!
Your mind is like a steel freakin' trap tawny!
I'm confused.
Did you really watch the movie?
Rude!
Duh, I watched it!
I just suck at remembering all the teensy-weensy details, okay?
I was uber-invested!
But in the emotional way!
Each time there was a song, I cried my eyes out.
Eh.
Yes, you did.
It was awesome!
I loved when the witch walked out of the house and cast a spell on fluffball,
Yeri, without even looking!
She was so super cool!
And even though she only drinks black coffee,
she puts milk and sugar in it!
And the omurice she made was the stuff of dreams!
What a tsundere move! How sweet!
They showed all of that?
Yeah, they did!
They only flashed it on the screen for a split second, though.
And at the end, did you catch all of the dishes on the table?
That part totally made me squee!
There were enough for the whole family,
so we get the idea they'll be together forever!
It made me super happy!
Oh, I see.
So that's why they showed us those details.
Without you here, I'd have no clue.
It was a good movie.
No doi!
How the turntables!
Did you really watch the movie?
I'm sorry.
I guess the movie didn't strike a chord for Tawny like it did for me.
Somehow, it feels like it went by in a flash.
I was nervous, but it was so much fun.
I ate what I wanted to eat.
Went to shops I wanted to shop at.
Saw a movie I wanted to see.
Huh?
Was it all geared towards me?
That was quick, too.
Guess today is over.
It'd be nice if we could stretch out our walk home.
Till the spending time can be stacked towards me.
It's on planned one hand, but I didn't trust.
It was 쏟 it for early days after we moved from the Absolutely partners.
She never really made a story now.
I guess that's the story.
I felt a little bit near this, and that's what and that does it.
Hey, Tawny.
Today was awesome!
But, uh, I feel like I might have dragged you around a bit.
Suzuki?
The shops we went to in the movie we watched were a bit beyond my usual tastes.
If I had been alone today, I probably would have picked different ones.
But I really enjoyed them.
That said, you were there.
If it had just been me, it wouldn't have been the same.
Those shops in that movie wouldn't have let the impact they did.
What I'm saying is...
I had fun today because you were there with me.
So thanks.
Hey, Tawny!
You think we could take a picture?
Huh? Right here?
Anywhere is fine.
I just know in the future, I'm gonna want to look back on today.
It was our first date after all, and I want to remember the fun and flirting and heart flutters.
Like a record of our love story.
Okay then.
Should we post?
Yeah.
You stand here and angle your face a little more this way.
Okay.
Here we go.
Well, good night, Tawny.
I guess I'll see you at school.
That's cute.
I like pandas.
Huh?
You mean it?
Yeah, I do.
I'm so happy at the time!
What's happening right now?
Tawny makes me feel like a glitter bomb about to explode!
I like myself way better when I'm all sparkly!
I'm the king of the girlfriends!
And the ultimate version of me!
I'm here!
Welcome back!
Dinner isn't quite ready yet.
That's fine!
No rush, mother!
I still need to check on our picture!
Kill me.
See you next time.